A Guide to the Richard Harding Davis Collection 1869-[1893]
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Richard Harding Davis Collection 1869-[1893]
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
6109-w
This holding consists of 9 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Contents List
- Portraits of Richard Harding Davis
  9 portrait illustrations, clipped from an article in an unidentified magazine.
  - "Age 5" July, 1869 (Box 16)
  - "Age 9" 1873 (Box 16)
  - "Age 18" 1888 (Box 16)
    With his brother Charles Belmont Davis, the present Consul to Florence, Italy. Photograph taken at Lehigh University.
  - "Age 22" 1886
  - Richard Harding Davis in disguise n.d. (Box 16)
    In this photograph, Davis is "in the disguise of a burglar, under which, as a reporter for the Press, he lived among the thieves of Philadelphia."
  - "Age 24" 1888 (Box 16)
    "A reporter on the New York Evening Sun. From a photograph by William M. Ruschhaupt, New York."
  - "Age 26" 1890 (Box 16)
    "Gathering material for The West from a Car Window."
  - "At the present time, age 29" [1893] (Box 16)
    "From a photograph by Pach."
  - "Age 29" [1893] (Box 16)
    Not identical to the preceding image, but apparently taken at the same sitting.